General Still Photograph Collection
General Still Photograph Collection
1957-1958
Unknown
3 linear ft. (5 binders, approx. 960 photographs)
Collection of still photographs of television and movie personalities, most from appearances on various television shows. Origin unknown.
2534123
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The General Still Photograph Collection contains approximately 960 photographs of movie and television personalities, including actors, comedians, journalists, singers, and talk show hosts. Photographs are housed in five binders and are referred to by binder and photograph number -- for example, "5-24" means binder #5, photo #24.
Arrangement of the Collection
The photographs are arranged in the binders in no particular order. To simplify locating a particular person, the inventory below is given in alphabetical order by last name.
Subject and Genre Headings
Radio, television, film; Popular culture; Dance and theatre; Comedians -- Photographs.; Motion picture actors and actresses -- Photographs.; Television news anchors -- Photographs.; Television actors and actresses -- Photographs.; Photographs.; Entertainers.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Inventory
- Photographs
  - Ace, Rosemary - ABC, Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet: Fixing Up the Fraternity House (Box 1)
  - Adams, Casey - CBS, Schlitz Playhouse: Carriage from Britain, 8/23/57 (Box 1)
  - Adams, Edie - NBC, Chevy Show, 5/29/58 (Box 1)
  - Agar, John - CBS, Gale Storm Show (Box 1)
  - Alberghetti, Anna Maria - CBS, DuPont Show of the Month: Aladdin, 2/3/58 (Box 2)
  - Alberghetti, Anna Maria - NBC, Bob Hope Buick Show: Roberta, 8/29/58 (Box 1)
  - Alberghetti, Anna Maria - NBC, Bob Hope Buick Show: Roberta, 8/29/58 (Box 1)
  - Albertson, Jack - NBC, Shirley Temple's Storybook: Land of Green Ginger (Box 1)
  - Albertson, Mabel - CBS, Those Whiting Girls, 6/14/57 (Box 2)
  - Alexander, Ben - NBC, Dragnet, 4/25/58 (Box 1)
  - Alexander, Johnny - NBC, Cosi Fan Tutte, 3/7/58 (Box 1)
  - Alexanderson, Capt. - CBS, Let's Take a Trip: S.S. United States, 1/22/58 (Box 2)
  - Allen, Steve - NBC, Steve Allen Show, 1/24/58 (Box 2)
  - Allen, Steve - NBC, Steve Allen Show, 5/16/58 (Box 1)
  - Allen, Valerie - CBS, Burns and Allen Show, 7/11/58 (Box 1)
  - Allison, Jean - CBS, Schlitz Playhouse: Hands of the Enemy, 8/2/57 (Box 2)
  - Ameche, Don - NBC, Don Ameche's Real Life Stories (radio broadcast), 4/4/58 (Box 1)
  - Ames, Teal - CBS, Edge of the Night, 4/28/58 (Box 1)
  - Anderson, Warner - CBS, Lineup, 9/5/58 (Box 1)
  - Andes, Keith - CBS, Playhouse 90: Homeward Borne, 8/8/57 (Box 1)
  - Andrews, Dana - NBC, Playhouse 90: Right Hand Man, 7/15/58 (Box 1)
  - Andrews, Laverne - CBS, Jimmy Dean Show, 7/15/57 (Box 2)
  - Andrews, Maxine - CBS, Jimmy Dean Show, 7/15/57 (Box 2)
  - Andrews, Patty - CBS, Jimmy Dean Show, 7/15/57 (Box 2)
  - Anka, Paul - CBS, Ed Sullivan Show, 1/23/58 (Box 2)
  - Arden, Eve - CBS, Eve Arden Show, 8/22/57 (Box 1)
  - Arms, Russell - CBS, Gale Storm Show: Lovey-Dovey, 7/25/58 (Box 1)
  - Armstrong, Louis - CBS, Timex All-Star Jazz Show, 4/11/58 (Box 1)
  - Armstrong, Robert - CBS, Climax!: Shooting For the Moon (Box 1)
  - Arnaz, Desi - CBS, Lucille Ball-Desi Arnaz Show, 1/21/58 (Box 2)
  - Arnaz, Desi - CBS, Lucille Ball-Desi Arnaz Show, 3/17/58 (Box 1)
  - Arness, James - CBS, Gunsmoke, 7/23/57 (Box 2)
  - Arness, James - CBS, Gunsmoke, 1/24/58 (Box 2)
  - Arquette, Cliff - NBC, Jack Paar Show (also shown as character Charlie Weaver), 3/14/58 (Box 1)
  - Arvan, Jan - CBS, Red Skelton Show, 5/15/58 (Box 1)
  - Astaire, Fred - NBC, An Evening With Fred Astaire (Box 1)
  - Austin, Gene - CBS, Jimmy Dean Show, 8/2/57 (Box 2)
  - Baer, Parley - ABC, Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet: Magic of Three (Box 1)
  - Baer, Parley - ABC, Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet: Record Trout (Box 1)
  - Baird, Jimmy - NBC, Decision: Sudden Silence, 7/18/58 (Box 1)
  - Ball, Lucille - CBS, Lucille Ball-Desi Arnaz Show, 3/17/1958 (Box 1)
  - Bancroft, Anne - CBS, Playhouse 90: So Soon To Die, 7/12/1957 (Box 2)
  - Banick, Bruce - NBC, Loretta Young Show: Day of Rest, 5/2/58 (Box 1)
  - Banks, Joan - NBC (shown with husband Frank Lovejoy and children), 3/7/58 (Box 1)
  - Bannister, Roger - NBC, Big Moment, 6/14/57 (Box 2)
  - Baragrey, John - CBS, Schlitz Playhouse: Sporting Chance, 8/16/57 (Box 1)
  - Barber, Red - NBC, Red Barber's Corner, 6/21/57 (Box 2)
  - Bard, Katharine - CBS, Climax!: On the Take (Box 1)
  - Bari, Lynn - CBS, Red Skelton Show, 5/22/58 (Box 1)
  - Barrett, Claudia - CBS, Trackdown, 4/17/58 (Box 1)
  - Barry, Jack - NBC, Tic-Tac-Dough, 8/2/57 (Box 2)
  - Barry, Jack - NBC, Twenty One -- Tic Tac Dough (shown with 7 other hosts), 7/3/58 (Box 1)
  - Barry, Jack - NBC, Twenty One -- Tic Tac Dough (Box 1)
  - Barrymore, Jr., John - CBS, Playhouse 90: Ain't No Time for Glory, 6/7/57 (Box 2)
  - Barrymore, Jr., John - CBS, Playhouse 90: Ain't No Time for Glory (with several men in background), 8/22/57 (Box 2)
  - Basehart, Richard - CBS, Playhouse 90: So Soon To Die, 7/12/57 (Box 2)
  - Bassett, John - WBZ/WBZ, Live Five (Box 1)
  - Baxter, Anne - NBC, Playhouse 90: Right Hand Man, 7/15/58 (Box 1)
  - Beaumont, Hugh - CBS, Leave It To Beaver, 5/27/58 (Box 1)
  - Becker, Sandy - NBC, Win With a Winner (shown with 7 other hosts), 7/3/58 (Box 1)
  - Becker, Sandy - NBC, Win With a Winner, 7/11/58 (Box 1)
  - Beer, Jacqueline - CBS, Schlitz Playhouse: A Contest of Ladies, 3/26/58 (Box 1)
  - Bel Geddes, Barbara - CBS, Schlitz Playhouse: Fifty Beautiful Girls, 6/21/57 (Box 2)
  - Bellamy, Ralph - CBS, Spotlight Playhouse: Model Wife, 6/19/57 (Box 2)
  - Bellamy, Ralph - CBS, To Tell the Truth, 7/18/57 (Box 1)
  - Bendix, Lorraine - NBC, Life of Riley: Movie Struck, 1/3/58 (Box 2)
  - Bendix, William - NBC, Life of Riley: Otis Yonder Story (Box 1)
  - Bennett, Joan - CBS, Playhouse 90: Thundering Wave, 6/25/58 (Box 1)
  - Bennett, Tony - CBS, Big Record, 8/21/57 (Box 2)
  - Benny, Jack - CBS, Jack Benny Program, 1/24/58 (Box 2)
  - Benny, Jack - CBS, Jack Benny Program (with band in the background), 4/7/58 (Box 1)
  - Benny, Jack - CBS, Shower of Stars, 3/26/58 (Box 1)
  - Benoit, Patricia - NBC, Today is Ours, 6/6/58 (Box 1)
  - Benoit, Patricia - NBC, Today is Ours, 6/6/1958 (Box 1)
  - Benoit, Patricia - NBC, Today is Ours, 8/1/58 (Box 1)
  - Bentley, Beverly - NBC, Price is Right, 8/9/57 (Box 1)
  - Berg, Gertrude (Kate Smith's Birthday Party), 6/10/57 (Box 2)
  - Bergen, Edgar (Kate Smith's Birthday Party), 6/10/57 (Box 2)
  - Bergen, Polly - CBS, To Tell the Truth, 7/18/57 (Box 1)
  - Berle, Milton - NBC, Material Witness (Box 1)
  - Berlin, Linda - NBC, My True Story (radio broadcast), 6/6/58 (Box 1)
  - Bernstein, Leonard - CBS, New York Philharmonic Young People's Concert (shown with children), 4/3/58 (Box 1)
  - Betger, Lyle - NBC, Wagon Train: Sally Porter Story, 3/14/58 (Box 1)
  - Bethencourt, Francis - CBS, You'll Never Get Rich: Bilko's Valentine, 7/15/58 (Box 1)
  - Bettger, Lyle - NBC, Court of Last Resort, 8/9/57 (Box 1)
  - Bible, Frances - NBC, Cosi Fan Tutte, 3/7/58 (Box 1)
  - Bickford, Charles - CBS, Playhouse 90: Clipper Ship, 7/25/57 (Box 1)
  - Bigler, Mary - NBC, Dragnet, 4/18/58 (Box 1)
  - Billingsley, Barbara - CBS, Leave It To Beaver, 5/27/58 (Box 1)
  - Bingman, Virginia - NBC, Queen for a Day, 5/23/58 (Box 1)
  - Birch, Paul - CBS, You Are There: Grant and Lee at Appomattox, 6/6/57 (Box 2)
  - Bishop, Joey - CBS, Keep Talking, 6/30/57 (Box 1)
  - Blair, Janet - NBC, Chevy Show, 5/29/1958 (Box 1)
  - Blake, Amanda - CBS, Gunsmoke, 8/20/57 (Box 2)
  - Blattner, Buddy - CBS, George Kell at Game of the Week, 4/3/58 (Box 1)
  - Bloch, Ray - CBS, Ed Sullivan Show (Box 1)
  - Bloch, Ray - CBS, Ed Sullivan Show (Box 1)
  - Bloch, Ray - CBS, Ed Sullivan Show (Box 1)
  - Bond, Ward - NBC, Wagon Train, 8/9/57 (Box 1)
  - Bond, Ward - NBC, Wagon Train: Major Adams Story, 3/28/58 (Box 1)
  - Boone, Richard - CBS, Have Gun, Will Travel, 8/15/57 (Box 1)
  - Boone, Richard - CBS, Have Gun, Will Travel, 1/24/58 (Box 2)
  - Boone, Richard - CBS, Have Gun, Will Travel, 1/30/58 (Box 2)
  - Boone, Richard - CBS, Have Gun, Will Travel, 5/8/58 (Box 1)
  - Boone, Richard - CBS, Have Gun, Will Travel, 5/22/58 (Box 1)
  - Borden, Johnny - CBS, Beaver Patrol, 3/25/58 (Box 1)
  - Borge, Victor - CBS, Victor Borge's Comedy and Music, 1/22/58 (Box 2)
  - Borge, Victor - CBS, Victor Borge's Comedy and Music, 1/29/58 (Box 2)
  - Boyd, Jimmy - CBS, Bachelor Father, 9/2/58 (Box 1)
  - Boyer, Charles - NBC, Alcoa-Goodyear Anthology, 8/9/57 (Box 1)
  - Bracken, Eddie - CBS, Studio One Summer Theater: My Mother and How She Undid Me, 7/26/57 (Box 2)
  - Bradley, Bart - CBS, Have Gun, Will Travel, 5/22/58 (Box 1)
  - Brand, Jolene - NBC, Queen for a Day, 5/31/57 (Box 2)
  - Brand, Jolene - NBC, Queen for a Day, 5/23/58 (Box 1)
  - Branningan, Hugh - NBC, Dough Re Mi (Box 1)
  - Braun, Judith - NBC, Shirley Temple's Storybook: Nightingale, 1/24/58 (Box 2)
  - Braun, Judith - NBC, Shirley Temple's Storybook: Nightingale (Box 2)
  - Braun, Judith - NBC, Shirley Temple's Storybook: Nightingale (Box 2)
  - Brinkley, David - NBC, NBC News: Huntley-Brinkley Report, 7/25/58 (Box 1)
  - Briscoe, Robert - CBS, Playhouse 90: Fabulous Irishman, 6/13/57 (Box 2)
  - Briscoe, Lord, Mayor - CBS, Ed Sullivan Show (Box 1)
  - Bronson, Charles - CBS, Millionaire: Story of Jerry Bell, 7/29/57 (Box 1)
  - Brophy, Sallie - NBC, Buckskin, 6/20/58 (Box 1)
  - Brown, Cecil - NBC, NBC News, 5/9/58 (Box 1)
  - Brown, John Mason - CBS, Last Word, 6/4/57 (Box 2)
  - Brown, Vanessa - CBS, My Favorite Husband, 6/12/57 (Box 2)
  - Brown, Vanessa - CBS, My Favorite Husband: Tea Room, 7/30/57 (Box 1)
  - Brown, Vanessa - NBC, Wagon Train: Sally Porter Story, 3/14/58 (Box 1)
  - Burke, Paul - CBS, Noah's Ark, 5/9/58 (Box 1)
  - Burns, Ronnie - CBS, George Burns and Gracie Allen Show, 1/31/58 (Box 2)
  - Burns, Ronnie - CBS, Burns and Allen Show, 7/11/58 (Box 1)
  - Burns, Sandra - CBS, Burns and Allen Show, 6/13/57 (Box 2)
  - Burr, Raymond - CBS, Perry Mason: Case of the Corresponding Corpse, 8/29/58 (Box 1)
  - Burton, Richard - CBS, Show of the Month: Wuthering Heights, 4/25/58 (Box 1)
  - Burton, Richard - CBS, Show of the Month: Wuthering Heights, 4/25/58 (Box 1)
  - Bushman, Francis X. - ABC, Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet: Bachelor (Box 1)
  - Button, Dick - NBC, Hallmark Hall of Fame: Hans Brinker or The Silver Skates, 1/10/58 (Box 2)
  - Buttons, Red - NBC, Hansel and Gretel (also on radio), 4/4/58 (Box 1)
  - Buttons, Red - NBC, Hansel and Gretel (also on radio), 4/4/58 (Box 1)
  - Byington, Spring - CBS, December Bride, 2/6/58 (Box 2)
  - Byington, Spring - CBS, December Bride, 4/2/58 (Box 1)
  - Cady, Frank - ABC, Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet: Magic of Three (Box 1)
  - Cady, Frank - ABC, Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet: Safe (Box 2)
  - Caine, Howard - NBC, Californians, 5/22/58 (Box 1)
  - Calhoun, Rory - CBS, Schlitz Playhouse: Curfew at Midnight, 6/10/58 (Box 1)
  - Calhoun, Rory - CBS, Texan
  - Carey, Macdonald - CBS, Undercurrent: Live Bait, 8/9/57 (Box 1)
  - Carey, Macdonald - CBS, Playhouse 90: Natchez, 5/14/57 (Box 1)
  - Carlisle, Kitty - CBS, To Tell the Truth, 7/18/57 (Box 1)
  - Carney, Art - CBS, Fabulous Irishman, 6/11/57 (Box 2)
  - Carney, Art - CBS, DuPont Show of the Month: Harvey (shown with Harvey, a bunny), 9/5/58 (Box 1)
  - Carradine, John - CBS, Gunsmoke, 7/23/57 (Box 2)
  - Carroll, Madeleine - NBC, Affairs of Dr. Gentry (radio broadcast), 5/16/58 (Box 1)
  - Carson, Jack - CBS, Schlitz Playhouse: False Alarm, 7/25/58 (Box 1)
  - Carson, Jeannie - NBC, Wagon Train: Annie MacGregor Story, 1/10/58 (Box 2)
  - Carson, Ken - CBS, Garry Moore Show, 8/14/57 (Box 2)
  - Cartwright, Angela - CBS, Danny Thomas Show, 1/16/58 (Box 2)
  - Cartwright, Lynn - NBC, Alfred Hitchcock Presents: Equalizer, 1/27/58 (Box 2)
  - Caulfield, Joan - NBC, Sally, 8/9/57 (Box 1)
  - Cerf, Bennett - CBS, What's My Line, 8/21/57 (Box 2)
  - Champion, Gower - NBC, Perry Como Show, 3/21/58 (Box 1)
  - Champion, Marge - NBC, Perry Como Show, 3/21/58 (Box 1)
  - Chapin, Joni - NBC, Julius La Rosa Show, 7/5/57 (Box 2)
  - Chapin, Lauren - NBC, Father Knows Best: Friend in Need, A (shown with the dog, Duchess), 3/14/58 (Box 1)
  - Chapman, Lonny - NBC, Investigator, 5/29/58 (Box 1)
  - Chase, Barrie - NBC, Evening With Fred Astaire, An (Box 1)
  - Chase, Ilka - NBC, Masquerade Party, 7/17/57 (Box 2)
  - Chauvin, Lilyan - NBC, Californians: Man From Paris, 1/10/58 (Box 2)
  - Christensen, Carol - NBC, Dotto, 8/1/58 (Box 1)
  - Churchill, Sir Winston - CBS, Twentieth Century (shown also with car and missiles) (Box 2)
  - Cianelli, Eduardo - CBS, Have Gun, Will Travel, 1/24/58 (Box 2)
  - Clark, Dane - NBC, Destiny, 7/15/57 (Box 2)
  - Cliburn, Van - NBC, Steve Allen Show, 5/2/58 (Box 1)
  - Clooney, Rosemary - NBC, Lux Show, 4/11/58 (Box 1)
  - Coates, Phyllis - CBS, Gunsmoke, 1/24/58 (Box 2)
  - Colbert, Claudette - CBS, General Electric Theater: Last Town Car, 2/4/58 (Box 2)
  - Cole, Nat "King" - NBC, Nat" King" Cole Show, 6/28/57 (Box 2)
  - Collyer, Bud - CBS, To Tell the Truth, 7/18/57 (Box 1)
  - Conreid, Hans - NBC, Hansel and Gretel (also on radio), 4/4/58 (Box 1)
  - Convey, Bert - CBS, Art Linkletter's House Party, 6/11/57 (Box 2)
  - Conway, Pat - CBS, Spotlight Playhouse: Model Wife, 6/19/57 (Box 2)
  - Cook, Barbara - CBS, Alfred Hitchcock Presents: Little Sleep, 6/3/57 (Box 2)
  - Cook, Barbara - NBC, Hansel and Gretel (also on radio), 4/4/58 (Box 1)
  - Cook, Barbara - NBC, Hansel and Gretel (also on radio), 4/4/58 (Box 1)
  - Copeland, Alan - NBC, Your Hit Parade, 8/9/57 (Box 1)
  - Corcoran, Noreen - CBS, Bachelor Father, 9/2/58 (Box 1)
  - Cordell, Carl - NBC, Lucky Partners!, 6/6/58 (Box 1)
  - Cordell, Carl - NBC, Lucky Partners! (shown with 7 other hosts), 7/3/58 (Box 1)
  - Corey, Jill - NBC, Your Hit Parade, 8/9/57 (Box 1)
  - Cotton, Joseph - NBC, Joseph Cotton Show On Trial, 1957 (Box 2)
  - Cotton, Joseph - CBS, Playhouse 90: Edge of Innocence, 7/1/58 (Box 1)
  - Coulter, Dorothy - NBC, Rigoletto, 1/24/58 (Box 2)
  - Cousins, Julie - NBC, Julius La Rosa Show, 7/5/57 (Box 2)
  - Crabbe, Buster - NBC, Captain Gallant of the Foreign Legion, 1957 (Box 2)
  - Craig, James - CBS, Millionaire: Story of Jane Carr, 7/8/57 (Box 2)
  - Crain, Jeanne - CBS, Playhouse 90: Great Gatsby, 6/16/58 (Box 1)
  - Crawford, Diana - ABC, Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet: Ricky is Micky (Box 1)
  - Cronkite, Walter - CBS, Twentieth Century (shown also with car and missiles) (Box 2)
  - Crosby, Bob - CBS, CBS Radio Program (with the rest of his family), 7/14/53 (Box 1)
  - Crosby, Bob - NBC, Bob Crosby Show, 7/11/58 (Box 1)
  - Crowley, Kathleen - NBC, Suspicion: Eye for Eye, 5/23/58 (Box 1)
  - Cullen, Bill - NBC, Price Is Right, 1957 (Box 2)
  - Cullen, Bill - NBC, Price is Right, 8/9/57 (Box 1)
  - Cullen, Bill - NBC, Price is Right, 2/6/58 (Box 2)
  - Culp, Robert - CBS, Trackdown: Trail, 2/7/57 (Box 2)
  - Culp, Robert - CBS, Trackdown, 4/17/58 (Box 1)
  - Cummings, Bob - NBC, Bob Cummings Show (shown with 3 women), 8/9/57 (Box 1)
  - Cummings, Robert - CBS, Schlitz Playhouse: One Left Over, 7/12/57 (Box 2)
  - Curtin, Phyllis - NBC, Cosi Fan Tutte, 3/7/58 (Box 1)
  - Curtis, Tony - CBS, Schlitz Playhouse: Man On A Rack, 2/4/58 (Box 2)
  - Cypher, Jon - CBS, United States Steel Hour: Upbeat, 6/7/57 (Box 2)
  - Dahl, Arlene - NBC, Max Factor Presents Opening Night (Box 1)
  - Dahl, Arlene - NBC, Max Factor Presents Opening Night (Box 1)
  - Daly, John - CBS, What's My Line, 8/21/57 (Box 2)
  - Damone, Vic - CBS, Vic Damone Show, 6/19/57 (Box 2)
  - Dan, Judy - ABC, Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet (Box 2)
  - Dana, Leora - NBC, Shirley Temple's Storybook: Rip Van Winkle, 4/11/58 (Box 1)
  - Dana, Leora - NBC, Shirley Temple's Storybook: Rip Van Winkle, 4/11/58 (Box 1)
  - Daniels, Lisa - NBC, Shirley Temple's Storybook: Magic Fishbone, 8/1/58 (Box 1)
  - Daniels, Lisa - CBS, Millionaire, 8/13/58 (Box 1)
  - Dano, Royal - CBS, Schlitz Playhouse: Fifty Beautiful Girls, 6/21/57 (Box 2)
  - D'Arcy, Georgine - CBS, Danny Thomas Show, 4/24/58 (Box 1)
  - Darnell, Linda - CBS, Playhouse 90: Homeward Borne, 8/8/57 (Box 1)
  - Dary, Alan - WBZ/WBZ, Live Five (Box 1)
  - Davis, Janette - CBS, Arthur Godfrey's Talent Search, 5/15/58 (Box 1)
  - Davis, Ossie - NBC, Emperor Jones (Box 1)
  - Dayton, Danny - CBS, Keep Talking, 6/30/58 (Box 1)
  - de Carlo, Yvonne - CBS, Playhouse 90: Verdict of Three, 4/11/58 (Box 1)
  - de la Torre, Rey - CBS, Studio One Summer Theater: Guitar, 8/16/57 (Box 2)
  - de Lappe, Gemze - CBS, Seven Lively Arts: Gold Rush, 1/24/58 (Box 2)
  - De Witt, George - CBS, Name That Tune, 1/17/58 (Box 2)
  - De Witt, Jay - CBS, Name That Tune, 1/17/58 (Box 2)
  - Dean, Jimmy - CBS, Jimmy Dean Show, 5/31/57 (Box 2)
  - Dean, Jimmy - CBS, Jimmy Dean Show, 9/2/58 (Box 1)
  - del Rio, Dolores - CBS, Schlitz Playhouse: Old Spanish Custom, 8/30/57 (Box 2)
  - Della Joio, Norman - CBS, Seven Lively Arts: Profile of a Composer, 2/5/58 (Box 2)
  - Deming, Millicent - NBC, Queen for a Day, 5/23/58 (Box 1)
  - deSuze, Carl - WBZ/WBZ, Live Five (Box 1)
  - Diamond, Bobby - NBC, Fury, 1957 (Box 2)
  - Dickinson, Angie - CBS, Millionaire: Story of Jane Carr, 7/8/57 (Box 2)
  - Dollar, Lynn - NBC, Lucky Partners!, 7/11/57 (Box 1)
  - Dollar, Lynn - NBC, Lucky Partners! (shown with 7 other women), 7/25/58 (Box 1)
  - Donald, James - CBS, DuPont Show of the Month: A Tale of Two Cities, 3/14/58 (Box 1)
  - Donald, James - CBS, DuPont Show of the Month: A Tale of Two Cities, 3/14/58 (Box 1)
  - Douglas, Paul - CBS, Playhouse 90: Dungeon, 4/3/58 (Box 1)
  - Douglas, Susan - NBC, Guiding Light, 6/13/57 (Box 2)
  - Downs, Hugh - NBC, Concentration, 7/18/58 (Box 1)
  - Draper, Charles Stark, Dr. - CBS, Conquest: Inertial Guidance The Ultimate Navigation, 3/28/58 (Box 1)
  - Dru, Joanne - CBS, Playhouse 90: Blackwell Story, 7/19/57 (Box 2)
  - Dubbins, Don - CBS, Climax!: Volcano Seat (Box 1)
  - Duff, Howard - CBS, Mr. Adams and Eve, 8/9/57 (Box 1)
  - Duff, Howard - CBS, Mr. Adams and Eve, 1/30/58 (Box 2)
  - Dunne, Ralph - NBC, Kitty Foyle, 3/14/58 (Box 1)
  - Durocher, Leo - NBC, Major League Baseball, 3/7/58 (Box 1)
  - Duryea, Dan (Box 1)
  - Edwards, Douglas - CBS, Miss America Pageant, 8/15/57 (Box 2)
  - Edwards, Penny - ABC, Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet: Cruise for Harriet, A (Box 1)
  - Edwards, Ralph - NBC, This Is Your Life, 1957 (Box 2)
  - Edwards, Seth - CBS, Beaver Patrol, 3/25/58 (Box 1)
  - Elliott, Bob - NBC, Monitor (radio broadcast), 4/11/58 (Box 1)
  - Elliott, Denholm - CBS, DuPont Show of the Month: A Tale of Two Cities, 3/14/58 (Box 1)
  - Elliott, Denholm - CBS, DuPont Show of the Month: A Tale of Two Cities, 3/14/58 (Box 1)
  - Engel, Roy - CBS, You Are There: Grant and Lee at Appomattox, 6/6/57 (Box 2)
  - England, Sue - NBC, Shirley Temple's Storybook: Land of Green Ginger, 3/21/58 (Box 1)
  - England, Sue - NBC, Shirley Temple's Storybook: Land of Green Ginger (Box 1)
  - England, Sue - NBC, Shirley Temple's Storybook: Land of Green Ginger (Box 1)
  - Engstrom, Jean - NBC, Shirley Temple's Storybook: Little Lame Prince, 6/27/58 (Box 1)
  - Engstrom, Jean - NBC, Shirley Temple's Storybook: Little Lame Prince, 7/9/58 (Box 1)
  - Erickson, Leif - CBS, Alfred Hitchcock Presents: Equalizer, 1/27/58 (Box 2)
  - Ericson, John - CBS, Playhouse 90: Innocent Sleep, 5/23/58 (Box 1)
  - Ericson, John - CBS, Frontier Justice: Stage for Tucson, 7/11/58 (Box 1)
  - Evans, Maurice - NBC, Hallmark Hall of Fame: Dial 'M' for Murder, 4/4/58 (Box 1)
  - Evelyn, Judith - NBC, Shirley Temple's Storybook: Sleeping Beauty, 5/16/58 (Box 1)
  - Eyer, Richard - CBS, General Electric Theater: Mister Kensington's Finest Hour, 6/27/58 (Box 1)
  - Fabray, Nanette - CBS, Shower of Stars, 3/26/58 (Box 1)
  - Fabray, Nanette - CBS, Shower of Stars (Box 1)
  - Fadiman, Clifton - NBC, Conversation (radio broadcast), 1957 (Box 2)
  - Farr, Felicia - CBS, Spotlight Playhouse: Model Wife, 6/19/57 (Box 2)
  - Farr, Felicia - CBS, Playhouse 90: Country Husband, 6/21/57 (Box 2)
  - Farr, Felicia - CBS, Playhouse 90: Natchez, 5/14/58 (Box 1)
  - Farrell, Charles - NBC, Charles Farrell Show, 6/21/57 (Box 2)
  - Faye, Joey - NBC, Shirley Temple's Storybook: Land of Green Ginger (Box 1)
  - Felton, Verna - CBS, December Bride, 2/6/58 (Box 2)
  - Fields, Gracie - CBS, DuPont Show of the Month: A Tale of Two Cities, 3/14/58 (Box 1)
  - Fields, Gracie - CBS, Studio One In Hollywood: Mrs. 'Arris Goes to Paris, 3/28/58 (Box 1)
  - Fields, Gracie - CBS, Studio One In Hollywood: Mrs. 'Arris Goes to Paris (six separate shots), 4/2/58 (Box 1)
  - Fisher, Eddie - NBC, Eddie Fisher Show (shown with George Gobel), 8/9/57 (Box 1)
  - Fisher, Nelle - NBC, Twenty One -- Tic Tac Dough (Box 1)
  - Fitzgerald, Ella - CBS, Big Record, 1/23/58 (Box 2)
  - Fitzgerald, Walter - CBS, DuPont Show of the Month: A Tale of Two Cities, 3/14/58 (Box 1)
  - Flood, Ann - NBC, From These Roots, 6/13/58 (Box 1)
  - Flynn, Errol - CBS, Playhouse 90: Without Incident, 8/15/57 (Box 1)
  - Ford, Betty - NBC, Ford Show, 5/31/57 (Box 2)
  - Ford, Doug - CBS, Master's Golf Tournament, 3/17/58 (Box 1)
  - Ford, Tennessee Ernie - NBC, Ford Show, 1957 (Box 2)
  - Ford, Tennessee Ernie - NBC, Ford Show, 5/31/57 (Box 2)
  - Ford, Tennessee Ernie - NBC, Ford Show, 1/3/58 (Box 2)
  - Ford, Tennessee Ernie - NBC, Ford Show (Box 1)
  - Ford, Terry - NBC, Twenty One (shown with 7 other women), 7/25/58 (Box 1)
  - Forrest, Sally - CBS, Climax!: Burst of Fire (Box 2)
  - Forrest, Steve - CBS, Playhouse 90: Clipper Ship, 7/25/57 (Box 1)
  - Forsythe, John - CBS, Bachelor Father: Bentley Loans Out Peter, 1/30/58 (Box 2)
  - Foster, Dianne - NBC, Opening Night: Sometimes It Happens, 6/27/58 (Box 1)
  - Fox, Sonny - CBS, Let's Take a Trip: S.S. United States, 1/22/58 (Box 2)
  - Francis, Arlene - NBC, Home, 1957 (Box 2)
  - Francis, Arlene - NBC, Arlene Francis Show, 7/12/57 (Box 2)
  - Francis, Arlene - CBS, What's My Line, 8/21/57 (Box 2)
  - Fraser, Liz - CBS, You'll Never Get Rich: Bilko's Valentine, 7/11/58 (Box 1)
  - Frederick, Pauline - NBC, NBC News (Box 1)
  - Freeman, Mona - CBS, Frontier Justice: Stage for Tucson, 7/11/58 (Box 1)
  - Furneaux, Yvonne - CBS, Show of the Month: Wuthering Heights, 4/25/58 (Box 1)
  - Furneaux, Yvonne - CBS, Show of the Month: Wuthering Heights, 4/25/58 (Box 1)
  - Gallant, Kathleen - ABC, Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet (Box 1)
  - Gallop, Frank - NBC, Monitor (radio broadcast), 8/2/57 (Box 2)
  - Gardner, Hy - CBS, To Tell the Truth, 7/18/57 (Box 1)
  - Garland, Richard - CBS, Climax!: The Big Success (Box 1)
  - Garrison, Keith, Lt. Col. - CBS, Air Power, 5/1/58 (Box 1)
  - Garroway, Dave - NBC, Monitor (radio broadcast), 8/2/57 (Box 2)
  - Garroway, Dave - NBC, Today, 4/25/58 (Box 1)
  - Garroway, Dave - NBC, Today, 7/25/58 (Box 2)
  - Gayle, Barbara - ABC, Adventures of Ozzie an Harriet: Fixing Up the Fraternity House (Box 1)
  - Gazzara, Ben - NBC, Three Plays by Tennessee Williams (Box 1)
  - Gersham, Jack - CBS, High Adventure with Lowell Thomas, 3/28/58 (Box 1)
  - Getteys, Bennye - CBS, Studio One Summer Theater: Love Me to Pieces, 7/8/57 (Box 2)
  - Gibbs, Georgia - NBC, Georgia Gibbs Show, 6/28/57 (Box 2)
  - Gibson, Hoot - NBC, Best of Groucho, 7/5/57 (Box 2)
  - Gibson, Virginia - NBC, Your Hit Parade, 8/9/57 (Box 1)
  - Gilbert, Johnny - NBC, Music Bingo (shown with 7 other hosts), 7/3/58 (Box 1)
  - Gillespie, Gina - NBC, Loretta Young Show: Day of Rest, 5/2/58 (Box 1)
  - Gobel, George - NBC, George Gobel Show, 1957 (Box 2)